we've been given
an example error message the error
message tells us
we've given a method the wrong number of
arguments
we've given it one argument when it was
expecting two reading line two of the
error message
it looks like this error is taking place
in the calculate product method
and it looks like we're invoking this
method on line four
i've written some code to produce this
type of error
i've defined my own calculate product
method and
it expects two arguments our parameters
are defined as number one
and number two however when i invoke the
calculate product method on line four
you can see that i've only passed it one
argument
the integer four so let's try to run our
code and see what happens
and we see a very similar error here an
argument error with the wrong number of
arguments
on line four where i invoke the
calculate product method
i can see that i've passed in only one
argument
my method was expecting two so i'll pass
in the second integer
and now when i run the code i expect it
to run without error
and it does
you